[DOOR OPENS]
- Howard, is everything okay?
- Yeah, baby, I'll be right in.
(Sheldon:)You brought a girl
to the Mars-rover control room?
(Howard:)Yeah, I picked her up in the bar.
She's a doctor.
(Howard:)One free barium enema...
(Howard:)...and my mother won't care
she's not Jewish.
(Leonard:)Wait a minute, so the eye patch
and the insults worked?
(Howard:)No, there were three other guys
with eye patches. It was a fiasco.
What did work was, "How'd you like to visit
a secret government facility?"
(Sheldon:)So, what exactly do you want us to do?
You help me get the rover out, and you get
Stephanie out before somebody notices.
(Howard:)She doesn't exactly have clearance.
(Sheldon:)Really? They don't let strange women
from honky-tonks...
...play with $200 million
government projects on distant planets?
(Howard:)Yes, I was bad. Maybe she'll spank me.
Can we please move on?
Hey, Howard, it's getting late,
so do I get to drive this thing or what?
(Howard:)Yeah, no, I'm sorry,
but something's come up.
(Howard:)Kind of a Mars rover...
Mars-rover-can-Howard-come-over...